thedailypage.com 2013-10-06

# Isthmus | The Daily Page -- Privacy Policy

The Daily Page, a product of Isthmus Publishing, understands that privacy is important to our readers and website users. Accordingly, we have assembled the following privacy policy. If you have any questions or concerns, please contact us at [tdp@isthmus.com](mailto:tdp@isthmus.com).

The Daily Page's goal is to provide readers with the information they want and need. To do that, we may gather some general information about those who access our site. We may place a "cookie" in the browser files of a user's computer, which will enable us to determine the user's operating system, browser type and version, ISP, top-level domain — such as .com, .edu, etc. — and other such general information.

Users have the ability to configure their browsers to refuse acceptance of cookies, which are pieces of information that sites transfer to a user's hard drive for record-keeping purposes during each visit. Cookies — which do not contain any personally identifying information — are a standard industry technology. A cookie cannot pass on a computer virus, or even capture your email address.

We will only collect personally identifying information that users voluntarily provide to us in registering for services (such as placing classified adverstisements), filling out surveys and entering contests. If you consent at the time you provide us with your information, we may also use that personal information editorially — to improve and customize our content — or we may employ volunteered personal information for marketing and promotional purposes. Isthmus and The Daily Page will limit internal access of user information to employees responsible for conducting business with our customers.

Web surfers should be aware that by voluntarily disclosing personal information on The Daily Page's — or any other site's — bulletin boards, those details can easily be collected and employed by third parties. Children should get their parents' permission before sending out any personal information, or making any purchases over the Internet.

The Daily Page provides links to several external websites. We cannot control and are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of these websites.

**Forum**  
Personal information disclosed during the process of registering as a user of The Daily Page Forum is considered private by Isthmus Publishing and The Daily Page. However, information posted to the Forum discussion boards is public information and can easily be collected by third parties. Users should exercise discretion when registering and posting to Forum. Children should get their parent's permission before posting to Forum. Isthmus Publishing reserves the right to use Forum posts to market and publicize The Daily Page.

**Newsletters**  
Isthmus tracks user traffic patterns from our newsletters. However, we do not correlate this information with data about individual users although we do break down overall usage statistics across all of our users and tally domain names, browser types, and MIME types which is obtainable from the browser string.

|
